http://drapes.com/privacy-policy

Menu
TableTable LinensTable SkirtingTable RunnersChair CoversPlacematsTable PaddingTable LinensTable SkirtingTable RunnersChair CoversPlacematsTable PaddingWindowPinch PleatRipplefoldPinch PleatRipplefoldBedDuvetsBed ScarvesBedspreadsPillowsDuvetsBed ScarvesBedspreadsPillowsBath & SpaTerry ClothBath RobesTerry ClothBath RobesConference & MeetingPipe & DrapeStretch CoversDropoversFittedInverted PleatConference ClothFittedInverted PleatConference ClothAudio VisualPipe & DrapeStretch CoversDropoversFittedInverted PleatConference ClothFittedInverted PleatConference ClothAudio VisualAudio VisualFast Folding Screen KitsSpeaker Stand CoversCart CoversLight Stand CoversSpeaker CoversProjector Stand CoversFlat Panel Mobile AV Cart CoversCart SkirtingTruss Covers3-Point Speaker Stand CoversFast Folding Screen KitsSpeaker Stand CoversCart CoversLight Stand CoversSpeaker CoversProjector Stand CoversFlat Panel Mobile AV Cart CoversCart SkirtingTruss Covers3-Point Speaker Stand CoversSodexoEntegra
Account
Settings
Language
English
Mexico
Currency
USD - US Dollar
EUR - Euro
Privacy Policy
Last updated February 21, 2019
DRAPES 4 SHOW’s Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by DRAPES 4 SHOW anytime you interact with DRAPES 4 SHOW, such as when you visit our Site, when you purchase DRAPES 4 SHOW products and services, or when you call our sales or support associates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at DRAPES 4 SHOW, and we go to great lengths to protect it. DRAPES 4 SHOW does not sell or rent your contact information to other third party marketers.
Personal Information
There are a number of situations when DRAPES 4 SHOW may collect information that specifically and personally identifies you (“personal information”). For example, we may request your personal information when you are discussing a service issue, participating in an online survey or promotion, registering to receive additional information regarding our products and services, sending a question, or purchasing a product. When you interact with DRAPES 4 SHOW, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, credit card information, information about products you use or own, and other information relating to a support or service issue.
DRAPES 4 SHOW collects your personal information because it helps DRAPES 4 SHOW deliver a superior level of customer service; it enables DRAPES 4 SHOW to give you convenient access to DRAPES 4 SHOW’s products and services; and it helps DRAPES 4 SHOW keep you posted on the latest product announcements, special offers, and events. DRAPES 4 SHOW may collect, generate, retain and use your personal information in connection with the facilitation, recording and processing of any requests, communications, or interactions you may have via our Site and for auditing, research and analysis to improve DRAPES 4 SHOW’s products and services. Unless otherwise expressly stated, personal information will be used for marketing and promotional purposes only by DRAPES 4 SHOW; provided, however, DRAPES 4 SHOW may also share your personal information with legal entities within the DRAPES 4 SHOW group globally, who will safeguard it in accordance with DRAPES 4 SHOW’s privacy policy.
Use of Cookies and Other Technologies
DRAPES 4 SHOW’s Site uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our Site are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. DRAPES 4 SHOW gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. DRAPES 4 SHOW uses cookies and other technologies to analyze trends; to administer the Site; to study the effectiveness of our online advertising and customer communications; to study traffic patterns on our Site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole; and to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us. If you prefer not to enable cookies, please disable cookies. Please note that certain features of the Site will not be available once cookies are disabled.
In some of our email messages, DRAPES 4 SHOW uses a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Site. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. DRAPES 4 SHOW tracks this click-through data to help determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked, simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email.
Automated E-Mail
You may request to join our mailing list and receive occasional e-mails regarding new site content or event information. To unsubscribe from this e-mail service, send an e-mail to staff@drapes.com with the word "remove" in the subject box. We will make reasonable efforts to delete your personal information from our database, but this may not be possible because of backups and records of deletions.
How Personal Information is Protected
DRAPES 4 SHOW takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.
Required Disclosure
It is DRAPES 4 SHOW’s policy not to disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties except as required or permitted by law or to comply with valid legal process, as requested or permitted by you, or if DRAPES 4 SHOW determines that, for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.
Policy Changes
DRAPES 4 SHOW reserves the right to make changes to the Site and to these Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy at any time by posting changes on the Site as appropriate.
Questions
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at staff@drapes.com.
TERMS & CONDITIONS  |
PRIVACY POLICY
